Kizaki-san has beautiful eyelashes.
لدى كيزاكي-سان رموش جميلة
And she can play musical instruments.
وتجيد العزف على آلات موسيقيّة
That was so good, Kizaki-san.
كان ذلك رائعاً يا كيزاكي-سان
I've been playing it my whole life. It better be.
هذا طبيعيّ. فقد كنتُ أعزفها طوال حياتي
She's so cool...
...إنّها غاية في الرّوعة
And she's my friend!
!وهي صديقتي
Hey, Akebi-san...
...أكيبي-سان
You've been looking at me a lot lately.
كنتِ تنظرين إليّ كثيراً مؤخّراً
Episode Six There's No School Tomorrow, Right?
الحلقة السّادسة لا توجد مدرسة غداً، صحيح؟
Next, the nationwide weather forecast.
فقرتنا التّالية، توقّعات الطقس على مستوى البلد
The rain we've seen between the Kinki and Kanto regions
المطر التي شهدناها بين منطقتَي كينكي وكانتو
will start to let up tomorrow morning,
،ستبدأ بالتوقّف في صباح الغد
bringing sunny weather to most of the country.
ليصبح الطقس مُشمساً في معظم البلاد
However, an area of low pressure in northern Hokkaido
غير أنّ منطقة ذات ضغط منخفض في هوكّايدو الشماليّة
Okay! I've made up my mind!
!حسناً! لقد اتّخذتُ قراري
may bring periods of less favorable weather for a time.
قد تمرّ بفترات يكون فيها الطقس غير مُستحبّ لبعض الوقت
Next weekend, I'm inviting my friend over!
!في عطلة الأسبوع المقبل، سأدعو صديقتي إلى منزلي
Now, let's take a look at temperatures.
والآن لنلقِ نظرة إلى درجات الحرارة
How many? How many?
كم عددهن؟ كم عددهن؟
One! I don't have the guts for any more than that yet!
!واحدة! لا أملك الجرأة على دعوة أكثر من واحدة بعد
Temperatures in western Japan will be two to three degrees higher than today.
ستتراوح درجات الحرارة في غرب اليابان بين درجتين إلى ثلاث درجات أعلى من اليوم
Erika-chan, right? The one you knew was interesting at first glance?
إيريكا-تشان، صحيح؟ مَن تعرّفتِ عليها كانت مثيرة للاهتمام من النّظرة الأولى؟
It might even be warm enough to break a little sweat in Kagoshima and Kumamoto.
قد يكون دافئاً بما يكفي لبذل بعض المجهود في كاغوشيما وكوماموتو
Yeah! I gotta go clean my room!
!أجل! عليّ الذهاب لتنظيف غرفتي
Eastern Japan should also be quite warm, just right for doing the laundry.
ينبغي أن يكون شرق اليابان دافئاً جدّاً وملائماً جداً لغسل وتجفيف الملابس
I'll help!
!سوف أساعدكِ
Finally, the week-long forecast, from Nagoya to Naha.
أخيراً، التوقّعات على مدى أسبوع من ناغويا إلى ناها
Wait, dinner's almost ready!
!لحظة، العشاء شبه جاهز
Later!
!إلى اللّقاء
Okinawa will see some very rough weather through the weekend.
سوف تشهد أوكيناوا طقساً قاسياً جدّاً خلال عطلة الأسبوع
Later!
!إلى اللّقاء
A week ago, I was full of confidence.
قبل أسبوع، كنتُ مليئة بالثّقة
(Mon.)
(الإثنين)
It's my first time inviting someone my age over to my house.
هذه أوّل مرّة أدعو فيها شخصاً في مثل سنّي إلى منزلي
Monday
الإثنين
Tuesday
الثّلاثاء
Wednesday
الأربعاء
Social Studies
دراسات اجتماعيّة
Japanese
يابانيّة
Phys Ed
تربية بدنيّة
English
إنجليزيّة
What should I say to get her to come over?
ماذا ينبغي أن أقول حتّى أدعها تأتي؟
Wednesday
الأربعاء
We can talk at school,
،يمكننا التكلّم في المدرسة
(Wednesday)
(الأربعاء)
(Thursday)
(الخميس)
and we can hang out during breaks between classes.
ويمكننا الخروج معاً أثناء الاستراحة بين الحصص
Hey, Akebi-san...
...أكيبي-سان
I kept thinking like that, and before I knew it...
...ظللتُ أفكّر في ذلك، وسرعان ما وجدت
Huh?!
!ماذا؟
(Fri.)
(الجمعة)
Hey, Akebi-san...
...أخبريني يا أكيبي-سان
You've been looking at me a lot lately.
كنتِ تحدّقين بي كثيراً مؤخّراً
Huh? N-N-No, I haven't!
!لـ-لـ-لا، لم أفعل
Yes, you have. You just were.
بلى. كنتِ كذلك
Is there something on your mind that's hard to say?
هل هناك ما يدور في ذهنكِ ومن الصّعب أن تقوليه؟
Well... There's no school tomorrow, since it's Saturday, right?
في الواقع... لا توجد مدرسة غداً بما أنّه يوم السّبت، أليس كذلك؟
Uh, right... Wait, why so polite?
صحيح... لحظة، لمَ هذه اللّباقة؟
Oh, um... uh... well...
...في الواقع... أنا
H-How do you feel about houses with leaky roofs?
ما-ما شعوركِ اتّجاه المنازل التي يكون سقفها نافذاً للمياه؟
Well, obviously, I think they should be repaired.
أرى بأنّها ينبغي إصلاحها بالطبع
No one wants to get all wet when they're inside.
فلا أحد يتمنّى أن يبتلّ بينما هو في الدّاخل
Y-You're so right! Yeah! That's what I've been wanting to ask you!
!مـ-معكِ حقّ! أجل! هذا ما كنتُ أريد سؤالكِ عنه
Akebi-san's acting weird.
تتصرّف أكيبي-سان بغرابة
I gotta fix that leak before I can invite her over.
سأصلح ذلك التسرّب قبل دعوتها إلى منزلي
Hey, Akebi-san...
...أكيبي-سان
I'm on my way to the school library next, so...
...أنا في طريقي إلى مكتبة المدرسة تالياً، لذا
Want to come?
أتريدين المجيء؟
School Library
مكتبة المدرسة
Introduction to Fishing
مقدّمة في صيد السّمك
She's still looking at me.
ما زالت تحدّق بي
That clearly wasn't all she wanted to say.
من الواضح أنّ ذلك لم يكن كلّ ما أرادت قوله
That looks like an interesting book you're reading.
يبدو كتاباً مثيراً للاهتمام تقرأينه
Have you ever gone fishing before?
هل ذهبتِ لصيد السّمك من قبل يا أكيبي-سان؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد
You have?
حقّاً؟
Yeah, at the lake near my house.
أجل، في البحيرة بالقرب من منزلي
The way I do it isn't that cool, though.
لكن لا أفعل ذلك بإتقان
I use a nice, bendy stick and sewing thread,
،أستخدم عصا متعرّجة وخيط حياكة
and leftover squid legs for bait.
وبقايا أرجُل حبّار كطعم
Her gear's all homemade?!
!كلّ عدّتها مصنوعة منزليّاً؟
But all I catch is crayfish.
لكن كلّ ما أصطاده هو جراد البحر
I've never once caught an actual fish.
لم أصطد سمكة حقيقيّة في حياتي
So when I go, sometimes I just wade into the water barefoot.
لذا عندما أذهب، أمشي في الماء حافية أحياناً
Barefoot?
حافية؟
I corner them, and Kao takes the net, and...
...أحاصرهم وتُمسك كاو بالشبكة و
That's amazing!
!هذا مذهل
Huh?
!هذه هي التّجربة التي أردتُ خوضها
I'm so jealous.
أغار كثيراً
Kizaki-san?
كيزاكي-سان؟
Um...
...المعذرة
If... you wouldn't mind...
...إن... إن لم تمانعي
I get it. I shouldn't just invite her to my house.
فهمت. ينبغي لي أن أدعوها إلى منزلي فحسب
Let's go together!
!لنذهب معاً
Maybe... tomorrow?
ربّما... غداً؟
Tomorrow?
غداً؟
There's no school tomorrow, since it's Saturday, right?
لا مدرسة غداً بما أنّه يوم السّبت، صحيح؟
Wait, is the reason you've been looking at me so much...
...لحظة، هل سبب تحديقكِ بي كثيراً
Quiet, please.
هدوء من فضلكما
A promise to meet up over the weekend.
وعد للاجتماع في عطلة الأسبوع
My first ever!
!أوّل اجتماع لي
I can't wait.
لا أطيق الانتظار
I never knew there was a place like this!
!لم أكن أعلم بوجود مكان كهذا
What a gorgeous place to meet up!
!يا له من مكان باهر الجمال نجتمع فيه
I got here a whole hour early.
وصلتُ إلى هنا قبل ساعة كاملة
The weather's so nice.
الطقس جميل للغاية
I wonder what Akebi-san will do when she sees this.
أتساءل ماذا ستفعل أكيبي-سان عندما ترى هذا
Maybe I should try to get acclimated to the water.
ربّما ينبغي أن أحاول التأقلم مع الماء
I don't want to look silly in front of Akebi-san.
لا أريد أن أبدو سخيفة أمام أكيبي-سان
Mom would flip out if she saw me doing this.
ستفقد أمّي صوابها إذا رأتني أفعل هذا
Oh, no... I can't stop myself.
لا... لا أستطيع كبح نفسي
It's my first time wearing this skirt Mom made for me!
هذه أوّل مرّة أرتدي فيها هذه التنّورة !الّتي صنعتها أمّي لي
I'm meeting Kizaki-san, after all!
!فأنا سألتقي بكيزاكي-سان في نهاية الأمر
I can't just show up in my usual sweats!
!لا أستطيع أن ألتقيها بملابسي المعتادة
I got here too early.
وصلتُ إلى هنا باكراً جدّاً
Huh?
ماذا؟
Kizaki-san!
!كيزاكي-سان
Are you okay?
هل أنتِ بخير؟
I'm fine... Akebi-san.
أنا بخير... يا أكيبي-سان
You're a good swimmer, huh?
أنتِ سبّاحة ماهرة، صحيح؟
Oh, I see now!
!فهمتُ الآن
You wore stuff that you can wear into the water!
!ارتديتِ أشياء يمكنكِ النّزول بها إلى الماء
Not a swimsuit or anything, but yeah.
ليس زيّ سباحة أو ما شابه، لكن أجل
Kizaki-san, thank you for coming to spend the day with me!
كيزاكي-سان، شكراً لكِ على المجيء !لقضاء اليوم معي
Same to you.
كذلك أنتِ
I asked where the best spot to catch fish would be.
سألتُ أين يكون أفضل موقع لصيد السّمك
It's a bit of a walk, though.
لكن يحتاج لقليل من المشي
Really? Let's go!
!حقّاً؟ هيّا بنا
You look really cool, Kizaki-san.
تبدين رائعة حقّاً يا كيزاكي-سان
I just bought this stuff.
اشتريتُ هذه الأشياء فحسب
I never get any chances to go fishing, though.
لكن لم أحصل على أيّ فرصة للذهاب وصيد السّمك
Today's my first time.
اليوم هو أوّل يوم لي
So I'm really excited.
لذا أنا متحمّسة حقّاً
Same!
!أجل
Well, the rod, too, but I was talking about the whole ensemble.
حسناً، السنّارة أيضاً، لكن كنتُ أتحدّث عن المجموعة كَكُلّ
R-Really? Thanks.
حـ-حقّاً؟ شكراً
I hope Kizaki-san will catch a big fish today.
آمل أن تصطاد كيزاكي-سان سمكة كبيرة اليوم
We'll catch something here for sure!
!سوف نصطاد شيئاً بكلّ تأكيد هنا
Okay, I guess I'll get ready, too.
حسناً، أظنّني سوف أجهّز نفسي أيضاً
Wait... Y-You're fishing with that?
لحظة... سـ-ستصطادين سمكاً بهذا؟
No rod or anything?
لا سنّارة أو ما شابه؟
Yep. It's rice. You can catch little fish with it.
أجل. إنّه أرزّ. يمكنكِ اصطياد سمك صغير به
I'll try over here.
سوف أجرّب هذا
Oh! I got one!
!اصطدتُ واحدة
You're kidding!
!تمزحين
I wonder what it's called.
أتساءل ما اسمه
Hang on! I'll look it up!
!انتظري لحظة! سأبحث حوله
A-Amur minnow...
...مـ-منوة الآمور
Freshwater Fish of Japan
أسماك المياه العذبة في اليابان
Minnow-chan! What a cool name!
!منوة-تشان! يا له من اسم رائع
Akebi-san's amazing, catching a fish with a thing like that.
أكيبي-سان مذهلة باصطيادها سمكة بواسطة شيء كهذا
I can do it, too!
!يمكنني فعلها أيضاً
There are fish here.
يوجد سمك هنا
That's for sure.
هذا مُؤكّد
Oh! Another Minnow-chan!
!منوة-تشان أخرى
And yet I...
...ومع ذلك أنا
It'll be hard to catch any with that bait. They can't eat it.
سيكون من الصّعب اصطياد أيّ سمكة بذلك الطّعم. لا يستطيعون أكلها
This is the only lure I have, though.
لكن هذا هو الفخّ الوحيد الّذي لديّ
How about the spot where that bird caught a fish earlier?
ماذا عن الموقع حيث اصطاد ذلك الطّائر سمكة قبل قليل؟
Yeah... but it's kinda far away.
أجل... لكنّه بعيد بعض الشيء
I feel like it's flying a little too high.
أشعر وكأنّه يحلّق عالياً جدّاً
Ease up a little and... let it fly!
!ارتاحي قليلاً... ثمّ دعيها تحلّق
Wow! You nailed it!
!مذهل! فعلتِها
I think it's stuck.
أظنّها علِقَتْ
I'll swim out and get it.
سأسبح وأحضرها
You don't have to go to all that trouble.
ليس عليكِ تكبّد كلّ هذا العناء
I'll see if I can't circle around to get it loose.
سأرى ما إن كان بمقدوري الالتفاف لإرخائها
Oh... Okay.
حـ-حسناً
Why am I so impressed by something like this?
لماذا أنا مُندهشة جدّاً بشيء كهذا؟
I'm so happy, though.
لكن أنا سعيدة للغاية
What? Stuck again?
ماذا؟ علقت من جديد؟
No... I got a bite!
!لا... أُكِلَ الطعم
You're kidding!
!غير معقول
I want to go back, but water's getting in...
...أريد العودة، لكن الماء يدخل
Kizaki-san?
كيزاكي-سان؟
Akebi-san! I got a bite!
!أكيبي-سان! أُكِلَ الطّعم
I need help!
!أحتاج مساعدة
Kizaki-san!
!كيزاكي-سان
I'm here!
!أتيت
Thanks!
!شكراً
Take over while I get these waders off.
خذي عنّي بينما أخلع الجزمة
Huh? Okay!
!ماذا؟ حسناً
Kizaki-san! What do I do?!
!كيزاكي-سان! ماذا أفعل؟
Okay, I'm back!
!حسناً، عُدت
I didn't know fish were this strong.
لم أكن أعلم أنّ السمكة بهذه القوّة
How do I reel it in?
كيف أسحب البكَرة؟
Kizaki-san, I'll catch it in this!
!كيزاكي-سان، سأمسكها بهذه
Almost there...
...شارفت على الوصول
Almost there!
!شارفت
We did it!
!فعلناها
Okay, say cheese!
!حسناً، ابتسمي
I can't believe it! A real fish!
!لا أصدّق ذلك! سمكة حقيقيّة
Wow, so this is what they feel like.
هكذا يكون ملمسها إذاً
She's really having fun.
إنّها تستمتع حقّاً
The speckles on its back are so pretty.
الرّقط على ظهرها جميلة جدّاً
Video
فيديو
But I feel sorry for it, keeping it in here.
لكن أشفق عليها بإبقائها هنا
So long. Thank you.
إلى اللّقاء. شكراً لكِ
There it goes.
ها هي ذي
Video
فيديو
We're gonna play in the water now!
!سوف نلعب في الماء الآن
Hey, Kizaki-san...
...كيزاكي-سان
Did you have fun today?
هل استمتعتِ اليوم؟
Yes.
أجل
A lot!
!كثيراً
Kizaki-san, do you need fresh clothes?
كيزاكي-سان، هل تحتاجين ملابس جديدة؟
I brought a set.
أحضرتُ طقماً
Is there a place I can change? And a bathroom?
هل من مكان يمكنني التّبديل فيه؟ ودورة مياه؟
No one'll see you over behind those trees.
لن يراكِ أحد خلف تلك الأشجّار
J-Just kidding.
أ-أمزح فحسب
We're almost to my house!
!اقتربنا من منزلي
Okay.
حسناً
I ended up heading to Akebi-san's house.
انتهى الحالُ بي بالذهابِ إلى منزل أكيبي-سان
And it's just to change clothes and use the bathroom.
وهذا فقط لتبديل الملابس واستخدام دورة المياه
Oh! Kao!
!كاو
Kao! This is Kizaki-san!
!كاو! هذه كيزاكي-سان
A tiny Akebi-san?!
!أكيبي-سان صغيرة؟
Mom!
!أمّي
Onee-chan brought her friend home!
!أحضرتْ أونيه-تشان صديقتها إلى المنزل
The building with the red roof that I saw on my way to the lake was your house?!
البناء ذو السّطح الأحمر الّذي رأيتُه في طريقي إلى البحيرة كان منزلكِ؟
Mom, look!
!أمّي، انظري
Wow, what a big butterbur leaf.
مذهل، يا لها من ورقة نبات الفوكي
Maybe I'll use it in a stew.
ربّما سأستخدمها في اليخنة
It's not an umbrella?
ليست مظلّة؟
Welcome. You must be the beautiful Kizaki-san.
أهلاً بكِ. لا بدّ وأنّكِ كيزاكي-سان الجميلة
You really are.
أنتِ كذلك بالفعل
Jeez, Akebi-san, don't describe me that way.
عجباً يا أكيبي-سان. لا تصِفيني بهذه الطريقة
Nice to meet you.
سررتُ بلقائكِ
Sorry to show up without noti—
—آسفة لمجيئي دون موعد
Mom, it was amazing!
!أمّي، كان ذلك مذهلاً
Kizaki-san caught a huge fish!
!اصطادت كيزاكي-سان سمكة ضخمة
Wow, how pretty.
كم هي جميلة
Is it a male char?
هل هو شار ذكَر؟
Right? I couldn't believe it, either!
!أليس كذلك؟ لم أصدّق هذا أيضاً
I wanna see! I wanna see!
!دعيني أرى! دعيني أرى
Uh...
...المعذرة
That's very impressive.
هذا مدهش جدّاً
All right, you two, go get showered and clean.
حسناً، أنتما. استحمّا ونظّفا نفسيكما
It looks like you went a little nuts out there.
يبدو أنّكما شاغبتُما كثيراً هناك
Erika-chan, the bathroom's over there.
إيريكا-تشان، الحمّام هناك
Oh... Okay.
حـ-حسناً
Kao, bring her a towel.
كاو، أحضري لها منشفة
Okay! Wait right here, Erika-chan!
!حسناً! انتظري مكانكِ يا إيريكا-تشان
Your mom is really nice.
أمّكِ لطيفة حقّاً
Akebi-san?!
!أكيبي-سان؟
You can use this.
يمكنكِ استعمال هذا
Take your time.
خذي وقتكِ
Thank you.
شكراً
This towel smells so nice.
رائحة هذه المنشفة جميلة
I'm a little nervous about being naked in someone else's house.
أنا متوتّرة قليلاً من التعرّي في منزل أحد آخر
Uh, Akebi-san, you can go first.
أكيبي-سان، يمكنكِ الذّهاب أوّلاً
They're both so unfair,
،كلتاهما غير مُنصفتين
using your first name the minute they first meet you.
تستخدمان اسمكِ الأوّل حالما تلتقيان بكِ
Is how they address me really that important?
هل طريقة ندائهما لي بتلك الأهمّية؟
Well... I hadn't given it that much thought before...
...في الحقيقة... لم أفكّر في الأمر مليّاً من قبل
But when I heard them call you by your first name,
،لكن عندما سمعتُهما تناديانكِ باسمكِ الأوّل
I felt really...
...شعرتُ
really jealous!
!بالغيرة حقّاً
Akebi-san didn't even hesitate.
أكيبي-سان لم تتردّد حتّى
Your skin is so pale, Kizaki-san.
بشرتكِ شديدة البياض يا كيزاكي-سان
You're so lucky.
كم أنتِ محظوظة
It's not getting in your eyes, is it?
لا يصل لعينيكِ، صحيح؟
No.
لا
The sponge doesn't hurt, does it?
اللّيفة لا تؤلمكِ، صحيح؟
I'll try not to make your skin all red.
سأحاول ألّا أتسبّب باحمرار في جلدكِ
Okay.
حسناً
Thanks. I'll wash your back next.
شكراً. سأغسل ظهركِ تالياً
No, you can get out and put your clothes on.
لا، يمكنكِ الخروج وارتداء ملابسكِ
I'll be out by the time you're done.
سأخرج عندما تنتهين
Okay... Thanks.
حسناً... شكراً
Kao! Show Kizaki-san to my room!
!كاو! دُلّي كيزاكي-سان إلى غرفتي
And have Mom bring up some snacks!
!واطلبي من أمّي إعداد بعض الطعام
You can toss your towel in the washing machine when you're done with it.
يمكنكِ رمي منشفتكِ في الغسّالة عندما تنتهين منها
Okay.
حسناً
Akebi-san's so good at looking after others.
أكيبي-سان ماهرة جدّاً في الاعتناء بالآخرين
Is she always like this at home?
هل هي هكذا دوماً في المنزل؟
She didn't even dry her own hair.
لم تجفّف شعرها حتّى
Thanks.
شكراً
I'm used to it.
أنا معتادة على ذلك
She wasn't kidding.
لم تكن تمزح
You're lucky you get your hair dried so carefully every time, huh?
أنتِ محظوظة جدّاً بتجفيف شعركِ بعناية في كلّ مرّة، صحيح؟
Uh-huh, but she doesn't use a brush with me.
أجل، لكنّها لا تستخدم فرشاة معي
She ruffles it up more.
إنّها تنفشه أكثر
Onee-chan's not acting like usual right now.
أونيه-تشان لا تتصرّف كالعادة الآن
She's trying really hard.
إنّها تبذل قصارى جهدها
Kao! You don't have to be that honest!
!كاو! ليس عليكِ أن تكوني بهذه الصّراحة
Hey, Kao-chan, tell me what you like about Akebi-san... I mean, your sister.
كو-تشان، أخبريني عمّا تحبّينه في أكيبي-سان... أقصد أختكِ
Aw, she even has the same mannerisms as Akebi-san.
وحتّى أنّ سلوكها مثل سلوك أكيبي-سان
Don't say anything weird!
!لا تقولي أيّ كلام غريب
Komichi, I brought drinks. Can you open the door?
كوميتشي، أحضرتُ شراباً. هل يمكنكِ فتح الباب؟
C-Coming!
!قـ-قادمة
Here you go. Snacks and coffee.
تفضّلي. طعام خفيف وقهوة
Thanks, Mom!
!شكراً يا أمّي
Thank you.
شكراً لكِ
Her butt makes a really good noise when you smack it.
تصدر مؤخّرتها صوتاً قويّاً عند الخبط عليها
Kao! That's not the kind of thing Kizaki-san wants to hear!
!كاو! ليس هذا ما تريد كيزاكي-سان سماعه
You do it all the time, though.
لكنّكِ تفعلينها طوال الوقت
Why would you do that?
لماذا تفعلين ذلك؟
When Kao was born, she did it to make her laugh.
عندما وُلِدَتْ كاو، فعلَتْ ذلك لإضحاكها
She's done all kinds of other embarrassing things, too.
فعلَتْ أشياء مُحرِجة أخرى كثيرة أيضاً
Want to see?
أتريدين أن تري؟
Aw, Mom!
!أمّي
Look.
انظري
And just look at this!
!وانظري إلى هذه
That's cute.
هذا ظريف
I wanted to look cool for her!
!أردتُ أن أبدو رائعة أمامها
Sorry we couldn't offer much hospitality today.
آسفة لأنّنا لم نقدّم الضّيافة الكافية اليوم
No, the coffee you gave me was great.
لا، القهوة الّتي قدّمتِها لي كانت رائعة
And now you're driving me home. This is more than enough.
وتقلينني إلى المنزل الآن. هذا يكفي وأكثر
Come visit again sometime!
!زورينا من جديد لاحقاً
Sure!
!بالتأكيد
Akebi-san, see you at school.
أكيبي-سان، أراكِ في المدرسة
Yep, see you.
أجل، إلى اللّقاء
Komichi-san! Komichi-san!
!كوميتشي-سان! كوميتشي-سان
Starting today, I'm gonna call you "Komichi-san"!
!"ابتداء من اليوم، سوف أناديكِ "كوميتشي-سان
So... you can call me "Erika"!
!"إذاً... يمكنكِ مناداتي "إيريكا
Okay!
!حسناً
Komichi, if you're going to bed, keep warm, so you don't catch a cold.
،كوميتشي، عندما تخلدين إلى النّوم دفّئي نفسكِ ولا تُصابي بنزلة برد
I will.
حسناً